<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
    <string name="app_name">Speedo Ring</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">403634893783263</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb403634893783263</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password ?</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="loin">login</string>
    <string name="or_connect_with">Or Connect With</string>
    <string name="facebook">facebook</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="remember_me">Remember Me</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t have an Account?</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an Account?</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="no_thanks_just_a_fan">No THANKS, JUST A FAN</string>
    <string name="this_information">This information will be Displayed as your Personal Data</string>
    <string name="success_is_where">Winners never quit and quitters never win. Complete your profile and keep track of your sporting.</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="birthday">Birthday</string>
    <string name="bio">Bio</string>
    <string name="club">Club</string>
    <string name="coach">Coach</string>
    <string name="main_sport">Main Sport</string>
    <string name="i_m_an_athlete_with_disability">I\'m an Athlete with disability</string>
    <string name="fans">Fans</string>
    <string name="_555">555</string>
    <string name="demo_text">Android library used to create an awesome Android UI based on a draggable element similar to the last
        YouTube graphic component.</string>

    <string name="timeline">Timeline</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="comment1">you have send comment successfully</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>

    <string name="empty_screen">Oops!! An unexpected error occurred</string>
    <string name="please_retry">Please retry after sometime</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="packers_movers"><![CDATA[Packers & Movers]]></string>
    <string name="tours_travels"><![CDATA[Tours & Travels]]></string>
    <string name="error_msg_unknown">An unexpected error occurred</string>

    <string name="verify_msg">Please type the verification code sent to</string>
    <string name="verification_code">Verification Code</string>

    <string name="toast_image_intent_null">Image picker option is missing!</string>
    <string name="lbl_set_profile_photo">Set profile image</string>
    <string name="lbl_take_camera_picture">Take a picture</string>
    <string name="lbl_choose_from_gallery">Choose from gallery</string>

    <string name="dialog_permission_title">Grant Permissions</string>
    <string name="dialog_permission_message">This app needs permission to use this feature. You can grant them in app settings.</string>
    <string name="go_to_settings">GOTO SETTINGS</string>

    <!--***********************************-->
    <string name="card_number">Card Number</string>
    <string name="mm_yy">MM/yy</string>
    <string name="card_holders_name">Name</string>
    <string name="cvv">CVV</string>
    <string name="proceed">Proceed with Card</string>
    <string name="example_name">Test Name</string>
    <string name="example_email">android-sdk-sample-app@instamojo.com</string>
    <string name="example_phone">9876543210</string>
    <string name="example_amount">10</string>
    <string name="test_description">Test description</string>
    <string name="pay">Pay</string>
    <string name="loader_message">Please wait&#8230;</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions"><![CDATA[Company means “Speedoring Technologies” and includes www.speedoring.com where the context so requires. Advertiser means the person, company or other entity that whises to advertise and avail of the services provided by the company and whose name is set forth adjacent to the term “ advertiser’s name” appearing overleaf. The rates mentioned herein are applicable for this transaction alone. The company will have the right to change the advertising rates at any given point of time without notice. All advertising material ( collectively “ advertisement”) supplied by advertiser to the company should either be owned by or be legally authorised for use by the advertiser. The Advertisement must not be obscene, offensive or uniawful in ant manner and should not contravene any applicable laws, rules and/or regulations The Company will have the sole discretion, at all times, to reject the Advertisement and further does not guarantee and particular position or place in the directory / website for the display of the Advertisement. Speedoring not Gurantee and do not intend to guarantee any business to its vendor, it is merely a medium which connects general public with vendors of goods and service listed with Speedoring. The Company will take reasonable precaution to publish the information, as supplied by the Advertiser, in the directory, However, the Company will not be responsible in case of any errors or omissions. The Company reserves the right to make any modification, if considered necessary or desirable in an Advertisement. Unless the Company and the Advertiser otherwise agree in writing, the Advertisement (excluding the trademarks and/or trade name of the Advertiser) used in preparation of the artworks will be the exclusive property of the Company, The Advertiser hereby warrants that the artwork design by the Company in any of its publications will not be reproduced or assigned for reproducing as a whole or in part, without the prior written consent of the Company. Advertising agency involved in placing the Advertisement for and on behalf of any person, Company or entity (”Ultimate Customer”) assures that it has the authority to modify and/or amend on Advertisement of an Ultimate Customer, in accordance with Advertiser’s instructions without committing any offence or tort. The Advertiser hereby warrants and agrees that it shall indemnify and hold the Company harmless to extent of any costs, damages or other charges falling upon the Company as a result of any claims and/or dispute raised by the Ultimate Customer against the Company arising from or relating to publication of the advertisement. The Advertiser hereby represents and warrants that 1. he is the owner of products and/or services that he wants advertised and/or 2. is duly authorised by the owner to use the Advertisement related copy cuts and illustration(s) and any trademarks & trade name which may be specified for use in the Advertisement. The advertiser hereby agrees to notify the Company in writing of any change in ownership or authorised as aforesaid, which occurs after the execution of this proforma invoice. The Advertiser hereby agrees to defend all its own, indemnify and keep the company harmless from any infringement claims, losses and judgements which are claimed to have arisen from use of such copy cuts, illustrations, marks and names and Directories, the Advertisement and/or any advertisement related material including but not limiting to any third party infringement claims together with expenses, attorney fees and court costs incurred by the Company. The Advertiser assumes sole responsibility and liability and liability for protection if its intellectual Property right(s) in any writing, pictorial illustration design format photograph or combination there included in the advertisement. Under no circumstances shall the Company or its associates by liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential or exemplary damages, ( even if the company has been advised of the possibility of such damages) resulting from or in connection with the use of by the advertiser of any of infocom’s services including but not limiting to damages(S) for loss of profits, goodwill, use, data or other intangible losses such limitation shall also apply with respect to damages incurred by reason of other services or products received through or advertised in connection with the company, regardless of any negligence arising out of any of its service. Without prejudice to aforesaid the company’s liability under any circumstances is limited to the amount if fees, if any, paid by the Advertiser to the company. In the event of any dispute between the Advertiser and the company’s liability under, in connection with or in relation to this proforma invoice, the same will be adjudicated by by the courts of competent jurisdiction at Delhi only, and in exclusion of all other courts that may have jurisdiction in the matter. This proforma invoice shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of india without reference to its conflict of law principles. In addition to the terms and conditions set forth in proforma invoice and unless repugnant to the meaning or context thereof, the Advertiser hereby agrees and acknowledges that the user Agreement/terms and conditions as reproduced on the speedoring.com website www.speedoring.com (”T&Cs”) are applicable to proforma invoice and are deemed to be incorporated here in by reference in the event of any conflict or inconsistency between this proforma invoice are the “T&C” the latter shall prevail. All correspondence to the Advertiser shall be sent to the address sent forth overleaf and all correspondences to the company should be addressed to our registered office.]]></string>
    <string name="about_us"><![CDATA[The challenging opportunities and new avenues cropping up in the corporate arena in diverse sectors demands the role of a common mediator to act as bridge between buyers and sellers, importers and exporters, and the like. This service facilitates all in the business world to come to a common platform, thus turning the geologically colossus earth into a tiny global village. SpeedoRing is a major entity involved in this task bringing manufacturers, buyers,retailers and sellers under one pedestal. SpeedoRing Technologies got established in the year 2017 and is identified by people at large as Speedoring.com thanks to our very popular B2C website of the same name. Launched in the year 2017 to offer the Indian Business community a platform to promote themselves globally speedoring.com has created a niche as India\'s largest B2C & B2B marketplace, offering comprehensive business solutions to the global EXIM community through its wide array of online services, directory services and facilitation of trade promotional events. Our portal is an ideal forum for buyers and sellers across the globe to interact and conduct business smoothly and effectively. With an unmatched expertize in data acquisition and online promotion, SpeedoRing subsumes a huge number of company profiles and product catalogs under 1,256 different product categories and sub-categories. The official website www.speedoring.com was launched in 2017. Speedoring’s search service is available to users across multiple platforms, such as the internet, mobile Internet, over the telephone (voice) and text (SMS).]]></string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Above charges are exclusive of service tax and advertiser’s are required to pay service tax over and above the actual charges a applicable from time to time. The above mentioned charges are for specified period only and if the advertiser wise to advertise any contents or material for any subsequent period then the advertiser required to pay additional charges which may be applicable at prevalent date, unless specifically agreed in writing. All information including texts and/or pictures to be provided by advertiser and advertiser must be legal owners/copyrights/trademarks holder of such design/picture/text or contents there of by whatsoever name may be called, in absence of legal ownership of such contents or materials, If any disputes or claim arises in future at any stage, the advertiser hereby undertake to indemnify the company in all means. The company shall not be liable or responsible for any such claim made by third party and any cost incurred by the company to defend the court case/suit or any proceeding shall be recovered from the advertiser.</string>

</resources>
